<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<scrolls>

    <event>
        <name>
About
        </name>

        <description>
"If there are no limitations to imagination, then there are no limitations to success." 
<br></br>
Imagination is a power, energy and a charm that can conjure one's potential to bear fruits. It allows the traveller to touch those intangible horizons that have always been mysterious for the rest of the world. Moreover, it has been rightly said that the seeds of imagination germinate only when sown in the soil of reason. Perpetually, the imagination and the clarity of thought helps to foresee the world in a better way but a question arises. 
What about innovation ?
It is the art which makes one perceive the world in a completely different way bringing the conceiver laurels to cherish for the rest of his life. 
Keeping this in mind, Ajay Kumar Garg Engineering College brings forth Scrolls (Students Creative and Oratory Learning Skills) '13-a national level technical paper presentation that aims in elevating your excellence to zenith, adding a facet to all the budding technocrats of tomorrow. 
The desire for knowledge is insatiable and to quench the thirst, we welcome all the budding pioneers and aces to a one day technical rendezvous where ideas will drive away all ignorance from our minds testing our preeminence in the field of Computing, Telecommunication, Information Technology, Manufacturing technology, Bio Technology along with advancement in Management fields.
So let us unite and explore all the unimaginable and untouched territories in the vast universe of science, surmounting the zenith of engineering and management, giving tech mongers a treat to relish upon.
        </description>
    </event>
    <event>
        <name>
Rules
        </name>

        <description>
Maximum of 3 and minimum of 2 authors per paper.
            <br />
            <br />

            <ol>
&#8226;For presentation, a time slot of 7 minutes + 3 minutes (for Question and Answer ) will be given to each team.

&#8226; A soft copy of the final paper is to be sent before the designated last date.Final paper should be uploaded on our website, in case you face any problem then mail it at scrolls12@gmail.com

&#8226; IMPORTANT::The paper should strictly follow the format of sample paper given on the website. 

&#8226; IMPORTANT::The paper to be typed in single space, double column format, using Times New Roman font and size 12. maximum number of pages to be 5 and the page should have no numbers.
 
&#8226; IMPORTANT::First page to include Title, Name(s) of authors, their college name, telenos as well as e-mail addresses 

&#8226; An LCD projector shall be provided for conducting the presentation. 
            </ol>
        </description>
    </event>
    <event>
        <name>
Contact
        </name>

        <description>
This will be updated shorlty meanwhile for any queries contact  SOFTWARE INCUBATOR
        </description>
    </event>
    <event>
        <name>
Dates
        </name>

        <description>
This will be updated shorlty meanwhile for any queries contact SOFTWARE INCUBATOR
        </description>
    </event>

</scrolls>